[
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9506ac",
    "correctAnswer": "Jason Bateman",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Javier Bardem", "Colin Firth", "Tim Roth"],
    "question": "Which actor has acted in both Arrested Development and DodgeBall: A True Underdog Story?",
    "tags": ["film_and_tv"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "63a039a6c7d86251f9b65c98",
    "correctAnswer": "Harold II",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "William the Conqueror",
      "Alfred the Great",
      "Edward the Confessor"
    ],
    "question": "What was the name of the last Anglo-Saxon king of England?",
    "tags": ["history", "britain", "uk", "monarchs", "kings", "saxons"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95064d",
    "correctAnswer": "Frances McDormand",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Rachel Weisz", "Frances Fisher", "Salma Hayek"],
    "question": "Which actress has featured in films including Fargo and Transformers: Dark of the Moon?",
    "tags": ["acting", "film", "film_and_tv"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950160",
    "correctAnswer": "Alexandre Dumas",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Victor Hugo", "Jean Paul Sartre", "Albert Camus"],
    "question": "Who wrote \"The count of Monte-Christo\"?",
    "tags": ["literature", "classic_novels", "arts_and_literature"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950807",
    "correctAnswer": "Asia",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["South America", "Oceania", "Europe"],
    "question": "The country of Turkmenistan is on which continent?",
    "tags": ["geography"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f56",
    "correctAnswer": "Isaac Asimov",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Ursula K. Le Guin", "Philip K. Dick", "Stephen King"],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Lucky Starr series'?",
    "tags": ["science_fiction", "literature", "arts_and_literature"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "625e9fb9796f721e95543fb2",
    "correctAnswer": "Red",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Yellow", "Gold", "Maroon"],
    "question": "Which of these colors would you find on the flag of Singapore?",
    "tags": ["flags", "geography"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a70",
    "correctAnswer": "Mother Teresa",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Florence Nightingale",
      "Marie Curie",
      "Margaret Thatcher"
    ],
    "question": "Who won the 1979 Nobel Peace Prize for her work among the poor?",
    "tags": ["history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6237410ccb85f7ce9e949d3d",
    "correctAnswer": "Laos",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Mozambique", "Brazil", "Zambia"],
    "question": "Vientiane is the capital city of which country?",
    "tags": ["capital_cities", "geography"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "6486be3159bc33d1c362f31a",
    "correctAnswer": "Paul Simon",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Elton John", "Billy Joel", "Bob Dylan"],
    "question": "Who won the Grammy Song of the Year award in 1970 for the song 'Bridge Over Troubled Water'?",
    "tags": ["music", "songs"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  }
]
